<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kauê Braga</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kauê Braga</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/en/posts/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/posts/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/about/</guid>
      <description>I have a masters degree in Transportation Engineering at Federal University of Ceará (UFC - Brazil) and am currently a research assistant at the Institute for Applied Economic Research (Ipea). I&amp;rsquo;m mostly passionate about data analysis with focus on data manipulation and visualization made in R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me, @johndoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/en/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/projects/</guid>
      <description>Interactive webapps Fortaleza&#39;s (Brazil) Public Transport System (SIT-FOR) Shinyapp with routes, bus lines and general information about SIT-FOR
  Access to Oportunities Project Shinyapp with results of IPEA&#39;s project Access to Oportunities. Won honoroble mention  at the Shiny Contest 2020. Made in partnership Rafael Pereira
     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
